{
    "id": "91b7d8448fd4403791fa9edebca1f0b1",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He supported his friendâ€™s claim.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "backed off",
                "backed up",
                "backed down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17c9e14296674028a7a22ae8d14c8e53"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police could not produce any evidence that would substantiate the charge of murder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bear out",
                "bear down",
                "bear up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d7d30107cf2f490ba2e93601d828ca2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want to sell my old car and buy a new one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dispose of",
                "dispose off",
                "dispose with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d84c79aa3f81445b9045a2370c8b0d4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "During her prolonged battle with illness she often desired death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "longed for",
                "longed on",
                "longed with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c17d482f50e46cb931b6ccb5d49599f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Athletes from our district won many medals at the national sports meet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bore away",
                "bore down",
                "bore up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a826bc728d324cfe979a8d66d64607e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The leader has been able to crush all opposition.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bear up",
                "bear out",
                "bear down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "628d62c0d3d840c588e7163dccd26092"
        },
        {
            "question": "He stopped suddenly in the middle of his story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "broke down",
                "broke off",
                "broke up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82d3a37afc844aab8ed231a8420f09fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "His folly has caused his ruin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "brought up",
                "brought out",
                "brought about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6da0768bd12d4fb68b56fa6698f7b70f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He found great difficulty in converting her to his views.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bringing her out",
                "bringing her round",
                "bringing her up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d13d56acc8ac4775b7d8fb3727e34cf9"
        },
        {
            "question": "His passion deprived him of his self-control.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carried him on",
                "carried him out",
                "carried him away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5dd32f91eabb4650841b3b9509767b1e"
        }
    ]
}